buycpanel.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy - BuycPanel

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

**_Entities Covered by this Privacy Policy and GDPR_**

The following entities are covered by this Privacy Policy and GDPR; Control Panel Solutions, Inc., JetApps.com, JetApps, JetBackup, BuycPanel.com, BuycPanel, MycPadmin.com, MycPadmin, JetClone.com, JetClone, and JetBackup.com

**_What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?_**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.

**_When do we collect information?_**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

**_How do we use your information?_**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

**•** To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

**•** To improve our website in order to better serve you.

**•** To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

**•** To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

**•** To quickly process your transactions.

**•** To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

**_How do we protect visitor information?_**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

**_Do we use ‘cookies’?_**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies, some website features will be disabled. It may affect the browsing experience and your user experience will be more efficient with cookies enabled, because some of our services will not function properly.

However, you can still place orders on the website without cookies.

**_We use cookies to:_**

**•** Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.

**•** Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.

**•** Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted

third party services that track this information on our behalf.

**_Third Party Disclosure_**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice.

This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you,

so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to

comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**_Third party links_**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**_Google_**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. You can view Google’s AdWords policies by clicking [**_HERE_**](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en)

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**_We have implemented the following:_**

**•** Remarketing with Google AdSense

**•** Google Display Network Impression Reporting

**•** Demographics and Interests Reporting

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**_California Online Privacy Protection Act_**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more [**_HERE_**](http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf)

**_According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:_**

Users can visit our site anonymously

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:

**•** On our Privacy Policy Page

Users are able to change their personal information:

**•** By logging in to their account

**_How does our site handle do not track signals?_**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**_Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?_**

It’s also important to note that we allow third party behavioral tracking

**_COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)_**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

**_Fair Information Practices_**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**_In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:_**

We will notify the users via email

**•** Within 7 business days

**•** Within 7 business days

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**_CAN SPAM Act_**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**_We collect your email address in order to:_**

**•** Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**•** Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders

**•** We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.

**•** Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred

**_To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:_**

**•** NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses

**•** Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way

**•** Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters

**•** Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

**•** Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly

**•** Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

**_If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at_**

**•** Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email, and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

**_GDPR Specific Guidlines_**

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below. Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.

Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

**_DATA RETENTION_**

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order nformation for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information and are a European Union (EU) resident.

**_EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield frameworks_**

As described in our Privacy Shield certification, Control Panel Solutions, Inc. and other covered entities identified above comply with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Frameworks as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland to the United States. Control Panel Solutions, Inc. and other covered entities have certified to the Department of Commerce that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/. We remain responsible for any of your personal information that is shared under the Onward Transfer Principle with third parties for external processing on our behalf, as described in the “Sharing your information” section. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit the Privacy Shield website.  
In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Control Panel Solutions, Inc. and other covered entities identified above commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Control Panel Solutions, Inc. at: Control Panel Solutions, Inc. 940 Calle Negocio Ste 150, San Clemente, California 92673, United States, sales@buycpanel.com, (877) 759-2783. If you have an inquiry regarding our privacy practices in relation to our Privacy Shield certification, we encourage you to contact us.We are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the US Federal Trade Commission (FTC). Our organizations commit to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) and comply with the advice given by such authorities with regard to data transferred from the EU and Switzerland. You may also refer a complaint to your local data protection authority and we will work with them to resolve your concern. In certain circumstances, the Privacy Shield Framework provides the right to invoke binding arbitration to resolve complaints not resolved by other means, as described in Annex I to the Privacy Shield Principles. If you have a data privacy complaint, you may file the complaint with the EU EDPS: https://edps.europa.eu/ or your local DPA: http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm. For more information please visit the Privacy Shield website: http://www.privacyshield.gov/list

**_MINORS_**

The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 18.

**_Contacting Us_**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

BuycPanel.com

940 Calle Negocio Ste 150  
San Clemente, California 92673

United States

sales@buycpanel.com

(877) 759-2783
